<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    app:layout_behavior="@string/appbar_scrolling_view_behavior"
    tools:context="com.example.ibm.pager_9_10.retrieval"
    tools:showIn="@layout/activity_two_fragment">
    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Welcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and dronesWelcome to Fall 2016 and Realtime and Embedded Systems course. This course deals with resltime and emebdded systems that are pervasive in our environment today. We will cover foundational concepts of (i) realtime systems (ii) embedded systems and (iii) realtime and embedded systems. We will also learn programming and control of variety of systems including (i) an Unix-like emebdded kernel (ii) internet endpoint devices and (iii) phones and drones" />

    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>